{"data":[{"question":"They share the housework ________ between them.","a":"equally","b":"equal","c":"they are equal","d":"and equal","answer":"1","explain":"\n- \"Share\" is normal verb- followed by an adverb.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"A well-known large natural lake is Lake Tahoe, ________ straddles the California-Nevada border.","a":"and","b":"which","c":"since","d":"for","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Which (pronoun): used as the subject in the non-defining relative clause\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Before ________, they used horse-drawn wooden carts.","a":"farmers have had tractors","b":"tractors owned by farmers","c":"having tractors farmers","d":"farmers had tractors","answer":"4","explain":"\n- They= farmers- subject in first clause must be \"farmers\".\u00a0\n- Simple past tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Tuna, ________, may weigh up to 1,000 pounds.","a":"is the sea giant","b":"can be giants of the sea","c":"one of the sea giants","d":"the sea of the giant","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Use a pair of commas in the middle of a sentence to set off clauses, phrases, and words that are not essential to the meaning of the sentence.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Physical fitness exercises can cause injuries ________ the participants are not careful.","a":"that","b":"to","c":"if","d":"with","answer":"3","explain":"\n- This is a Conditional Sentence type 1\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Total weight of all the ants in the world is much greater than ________.","a":"to all human beings","b":"all human beings is that","c":"that of all human beings","d":"is of all human beings","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Thing to compare must be equal- person-person; object-object... \n- Thing to compare in this case is \" total weight of\" - that of.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"________ for overall health.","a":"Extra fiber in one's diet is helpful","b":"Extra fiber is one's helpful diet","c":"Helpful one's diet is extra fiber","d":"One's diet is helpful in extra fiber","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n- Subject: Extra fiber in one's diet.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Elephants scratch themselves with sticks ________.","a":"holding in their trunks","b":"in their trunks holding","c":"hold in their trunks","d":"held in their trunks","answer":"4","explain":"- We use past participle to shorten the relative clause (passive meaning)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Van Gogh's \"Sunflowers\" ________ 39.9 million, three times the previous record.","a":"once sold for","b":"for sale once","c":"selling for once","d":"for once sold","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple past tense.\u00a0\n- Once + Verb in past form: in the past, at a time that is not stated.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Some monkeys, ________, use their tails in a way similar to a hand.","a":"like the spider monkey","b":"spider monkey likes","c":"to the spider monkey","d":"the monkey likes the spider","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Like + noun: similar to something else, or happening in the same way.\u00a0\n- When the sentence is separated by a pair of commas in the middle of a sentence, words lie between these two commas are not essential to the meaning of the sentence and they don't affect sentence structure.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}